Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Friends records, circa 1961-1995 COR0008.2.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Acquisitions, 1961-1978; Series 6
  Subject File. Correspondence, thank you notes, memoranda, press release, brochure, questionnaires, ballots, lists of works, sales contracts, invoices and sales receipts concerning the acquisition by the Friends of works of art to be donated to the Corcoran. Files are arranged chronologically and subjects included are: nomination and voting procedures, details on the artists and their paintings, and exchanges with the Gallery concerning the appropriateness or impact of the paintings.
  - Acquisitions, 1971 March-1978 March; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Acquisitions, 1961 October-1970 March; Series 6 (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Trips, November 1976-November 1977; Series 7
  Subject File. Correspondence, notes, brochures concerning Friends' trips to Brazil, Russia and Philadelphia.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - Other Trips FY84, 1984; Series 7 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous activities, February 1964-December 1973; Series 8
  Subject File. Correspondence and invoice for a film presentation and a memorandum concerning a slide lecture.
  - Miscellaneous Activities, 1964 February-1973 December; Series 8 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Clippings, 1964-1984; Series 9
  Arranged in original order.
  Clippings concerning exhibitions and other Friends sponsored activities, acquisitions, relations with the Gallery, and spotlights on major Friends personalities.
  - News Articles, 1964-1971; Series 9 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Portfolio Magazine, 1981-1984; Series 9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Events, 1968-1984; Series 10
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Contains material documenting Friends-organized and Friends-exclusive events.
  - Metropolitan, 1968-1969; Series 10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Events, 1983; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Events, 1983; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Ball, 1983; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Malcolm Morley Reception, 1983 September 9; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Marc Thompson/Friends project, 1983; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Programs, 1983-1984; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Events, 1984; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Events, 1984; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - M Deleted, 1984; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Motherwell function, 1984; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - DeKooning on DeKooning, Undated; Series 10 (Box 3, Folder 20)